<?xml version="1.0"?>
<pp.it.functional>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_ARP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_ARP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall take <span class="assign">list of the least disruptive actions</span> upon detection of a potential security violation.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_SAA.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_GEN.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_GEN.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to generate an audit record of the following auditable events:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	Start-up and shutdown of the audit functions;
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	All auditable events for the <span class="select">minimum, basic, detailed, not specified</span> level of audit; and
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	<span class="assign">other specifically defined auditable events</span>.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_GEN.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall record within each audit record at least the following information: 
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	Date and time of the event, type of event, subject identity, and the outcome (success or failure) of the event; and
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	For each audit event type, based on the auditable event definitions of the functional components included in the PP/ST, <span class="assign">other audit relevant information</span> 
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_STM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_GEN.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_GEN.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to associate each auditable event with the identity of the user that caused the event.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to apply a set of rules in monitoring the audited events and based upon these rules indicate a potential violation of the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following rules for monitoring audited events:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	Accumulation or combination of <span class="assign">subset of defined auditable events</span> known to indicate a potential security violation;
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	<span class="assign">any other rules</span>.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_SAA.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to maintain profiles of system usage, where an individual profile represents the historical patterns of usage performed by the member(s) of <span class="assign">the profile target group</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to maintain a suspicion rating associated with each user whose activity is recorded in a profile, where the suspicion rating represents the degree to which the user's current activity is found inconsistent with the established patterns of usage represented in the profile.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to indicate an imminent violation of the TSP when a user's suspicion rating exceeds the following threshold conditions <span class="assign">conditions under which anomalous activity is reported by the TSF</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.3">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_SAA.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to maintain an internal representation of the following signature events <span class="assign">a subset of system events</span> that may indicate a violation of the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to compare the signature events against the record of system activity discernible from an examination of <span class="assign">the information to be used to determine system activity</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.3.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to indicate an imminent violation of the TSP when a system event is found to match a signature event that indicates a potential violation of the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.4">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_SAA.3"/>
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_SAA.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to maintain an internal representation of the following event sequences of known intrusion scenarios <span class="assign">list of sequences of system events whose occurrence are representative of known penetration scenarios</span> and the following signature events <span class="assign">a subset of system events</span> that may indicate a potential violation of the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.4.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to compare the signature events and event sequences against the record of system activity discernible from an examination of <span class="assign">the information to be used to determine system activity</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAA.4.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to indicate an imminent violation of the TSP when system activity is found to match a signature event or event sequence that indicates a potential violation of the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAR.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">authorised users</span> with the capability to read <span class="assign">list of audit information</span> from the audit records.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAR.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the audit records in a manner suitable for the user to interpret the information.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAR.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall prohibit all users read access to the audit records, except those users that have been granted explicit read-access. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_SAR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SAR.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the ability to perform <span class="select">searches, sorting, ordering</span> of audit data based on <span class="assign">criteria with logical relations</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_SAR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SEL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_SEL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to include or exclude auditable events from the set of audited events based on the following attributes:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	<span class="select">object identity, user identity, subject identity, host identity, event type</span>
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	<span class="assign">list of additional attributes that audit selectivity is based upon</span>.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MTD.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall protect the stored audit records from unauthorised deletion.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to <span class="select">prevent, detect</span> modifications to the audit records.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_STG.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall protect the stored audit records from unauthorised deletion.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to <span class="select">prevent, detect</span> modifications to the audit records.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">metric for saving audit records</span> audit records will be maintained when the following conditions occur: <span class="select">audit storage exhaustion, failure, attack</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall take <span class="assign">actions to be taken in case of possible audit storage failure</span> if the audit trail exceeds <span class="assign">pre-defined limit</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_STG.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.4">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FAU_STG.3"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FAU_STG.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">`ignore auditable events', `prevent auditable events, except those taken by the authorised user with special rights', `overwrite the oldest stored audit records'</span> and <span class="assign">other actions to be taken in case of audit storage failure</span> if the audit trail is full.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FAU_STG.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRO.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to generate evidence of origin for transmitted <span class="assign">list of information types</span> at the request of the <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to relate the <span class="assign">list of attributes</span> of the originator of the information, and the <span class="assign">list of information fields</span> of the information to which the evidence applies.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to verify the evidence of origin of information to <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span> given <span class="assign">limitations on the evidence of origin</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRO.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FCO_NRO.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the generation of evidence of origin for transmitted <span class="assign">list of information types</span> at all times.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to relate the <span class="assign">list of attributes</span> of the originator of the information, and the <span class="assign">list of information fields</span> of the information to which the evidence applies.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRO.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to verify the evidence of origin of information to <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span> given <span class="assign">limitations on the evidence of origin</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRR.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to generate evidence of receipt for received <span class="assign">list of information types</span> at the request of the <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to relate the <span class="assign">list of attributes</span> of the recipient of the information, and the <span class="assign">list of information fields</span> of the information to which the evidence applies.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to verify the evidence of receipt of information to <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span> given <span class="assign">limitations on the evidence of receipt</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRR.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FCO_NRR.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the generation of evidence of receipt for received <span class="assign">list of information types</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to relate the <span class="assign">list of attributes</span> of the recipient of the information, and the <span class="assign">list of information fields</span> of the information to which the evidence applies.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FCO_NRR.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to verify the evidence of receipt of information to <span class="select">originator, recipient, <span class="assign">list of third parties</span></span> given <span class="assign">limitations on the evidence of receipt</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FCS_CKM.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall generate cryptographic keys in accordance with a specified cryptographic key generation algorithm <span class="assign">cryptographic key generation algorithm</span> and specified cryptographic key sizes <span class="assign">cryptographic key sizes</span> that meet the following: <span class="assign">list of standards</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.2"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_COP.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.4"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FCS_CKM.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall distribute cryptographic keys in accordance with a specified cryptographic key distribution method <span class="assign">cryptographic key distribution method</span> that meets the following: <span class="assign">list of standards</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.4"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FCS_CKM.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall perform <span class="assign">type of cryptographic key access</span> in accordance with a specified cryptographic key access method <span class="assign">cryptographic key access method</span> that meets the following: <span class="assign">list of standards</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.4"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.4">
    <pp.sfr name="FCS_CKM.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall destroy cryptographic keys in accordance with a specified cryptographic key destruction method <span class="assign">cryptographic key destruction method</span> that meets the following: <span class="assign">list of standards</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_COP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FCS_COP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall perform <span class="assign">list of cryptographic operations</span> in accordance with a specified cryptographic algorithm <span class="assign">cryptographic algorithm</span> and cryptographic key sizes <span class="assign">cryptographic key sizes</span> that meet the following: <span class="assign">list of standards</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FCS_CKM.4"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP</span> on <span class="assign">list of subjects, objects, and operations among subjects and objects covered by the SFP</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACC.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACC.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP</span> on <span class="assign">list of subjects and objects</span> and all operations among subjects and objects covered by the SFP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACC.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that all operations between any subject in the TSC and any object within the TSC are covered by an access control SFP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACF.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACF.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP</span> to objects based on <span class="assign">security attributes, named groups of security attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACF.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following rules to determine if an operation among controlled subjects and controlled objects is allowed: <span class="assign">rules governing access among controlled subjects and controlled objects using controlled operations on controlled objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACF.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly authorise access of subjects to objects based on the following additional rules: <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly authorise access of subjects to objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ACF.1.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly deny access of subjects to objects based on the <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly deny access of subjects to objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.3"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_DAU.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_DAU.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to generate evidence that can be used as a guarantee of the validity of <span class="assign">list of objects or information types</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_DAU.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">list of subjects</span> with the ability to verify evidence of the validity of the indicated information.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_DAU.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_DAU.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_DAU.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a capability to generate evidence that can be used as a guarantee of the validity of <span class="assign">list of objects or information types</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_DAU.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">list of subjects</span> with the ability to verify evidence of the validity of the indicated information and the identity of the user that generated the evidence.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ETC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> when exporting user data, controlled under the SFP(s), outside of the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall export the user data without the user data's associated security attributes.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ETC.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> when exporting user data, controlled under the SFP(s), outside of the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall export the user data with the user data's associated security attributes.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that the security attributes, when exported outside the TSC, are unambiguously associated with the exported user data.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ETC.2.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following rules when user data is exported from the TSC: <span class="assign">additional exportation control rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> on <span class="assign">list of subjects, information, and operations that cause controlled information to flow to and from controlled subjects covered by the SFP</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFC.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFC.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> on <span class="assign">list of subjects and information</span> and all operations that cause that  information to flow to and from subjects covered by the SFP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFC.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that all operations that cause any information in the TSC to flow to and from any subject in the TSC are covered by an information flow control SFP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> based on the following types of subject and information security attributes: <span class="assign">the minimum number and type of security attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit an information flow between a controlled subject and  controlled information via a controlled operation if the following rules hold: <span class="assign">for each operation, the security attribute-based relationship that must hold between subject and information security attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">additional information flow control SFP rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the following <span class="assign">list of additional SFP capabilities</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.5">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly authorise an information flow based on the following rules: <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly authorise information flows</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.1.6">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly deny an information flow based on the following rules: <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly deny information flows</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.3"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_IFF.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> based on the following types of subject and information security attributes: <span class="assign">the minimum number and type of security attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit an information flow between a controlled subject and  controlled information via a controlled operation if the following rules, based on the ordering relationships between security attributes hold: <span class="assign">for each operation, the security attribute-based relationship that must hold between subject and information security attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">additional information flow control SFP rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the following <span class="assign">list of additional SFP capabilities</span>
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.5">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly authorise an information flow based on the following rules: <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly authorise information flows</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.6">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall explicitly deny an information flow based on the following rules: <span class="assign">rules, based on security attributes, that explicitly deny information flows</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.2.7">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following relationships for any two valid information flow control security attributes:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	There exists an ordering function that, given two valid security attributes, determines if the security attributes are equal, if one security attribute is greater than the other, or if the security attributes are incomparable; and
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	There exists a ``least upper bound'' in the set of security attributes, such that, given any two valid security attributes, there is a valid security attribute that is greater than or equal to the two valid security attributes; and
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	There exists a ``greatest lower bound'' in the set of security attributes, such that, given any two valid security attributes, there is a valid security attribute that is not greater than the two valid security attributes.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.3"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> to limit the capacity of <span class="assign">types of illicit information flows</span> to a <span class="assign">maximum capacity</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AVA_CCA.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.4">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_IFF.3"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> to limit the capacity of <span class="assign">types of illicit information flows</span> to a <span class="assign">maximum capacity</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.4.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall prevent  <span class="assign">types of illicit information flows</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AVA_CCA.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.5">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_IFF.4"/>
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_IFF.3"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.5.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that no illicit information flows exist to circumvent <span class="assign">name of information flow control SFP</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AVA_CCA.3"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.6">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_IFF.6.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">information flow control SFP</span> to monitor <span class="assign">types of illicit information flows</span> when it exceeds the <span class="assign">maximum capacity</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AVA_CCA.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP and/or information flow control SFP</span> when importing user data, controlled under the SFP, from outside of the TSC. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ignore any security attributes associated with the user data when imported from outside the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following rules when importing user data controlled under the SFP from outside the TSC: <span class="assign">additional importation control rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.3"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITC.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP and/or information flow control SFP</span> when importing user data, controlled under the SFP, from outside of the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall use the security attributes associated with the imported user data.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that the protocol used provides for the unambiguous association between the security attributes and the user data received.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.2.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that interpretation of the security attributes of the imported user data is as intended by the source of the user data.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITC.2.5">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the following rules when importing user data controlled under the SFP from outside the TSC: <span class="assign">additional importation control rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_TRP.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_TDC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to prevent the <span class="select">disclosure, modification, loss of use</span> of user data when it is transmitted between physically-separated parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_ITT.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to prevent the <span class="select">disclosure, modification, loss of use</span> of user data when it is transmitted between physically-separated parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall separate data controlled by the SFP(s) when transmitted between physically-separated parts of the TOE, based on the values of the following: <span class="assign">security attributes that require separation</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to monitor user data transmitted between physically-separated parts of the TOE for the following errors: <span class="assign">integrity errors</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon detection of a data integrity error, the TSF shall <span class="assign">specify the action to be taken upon integrity error</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.4">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_ITT.3"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to monitor user data transmitted between physically-separated parts of the TOE for the following errors: <span class="assign">integrity errors</span>, based on the following attributes: <span class="assign">security attributes that require separate transmission channels</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ITT.4.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon detection of a data integrity error, the TSF shall <span class="assign">specify the action to be taken upon integrity error</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ITT.2"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_RIP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_RIP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that any previous information content of a resource is made unavailable upon the <span class="select">allocation of the resource to, deallocation of the resource from</span> the following objects: <span class="assign">list of objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_RIP.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_RIP.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_RIP.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that any previous information content of a resource is made unavailable upon the <span class="select">allocation of the resource to, deallocation of the resource from</span> all objects.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ROL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ROL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to permit the rollback of the <span class="assign">list of operations</span> on the <span class="assign">list of objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ROL.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit operations to be rolled back within the <span class="assign">boundary limit to which rollback may be performed</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ROL.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_ROL.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ROL.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to permit the rollback of all the operations on the <span class="assign">list of objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_ROL.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit operations to be rolled back within the <span class="assign">boundary limit to which rollback may be performed</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_SDI.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_SDI.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall monitor user data stored within the TSC for <span class="assign">integrity errors</span> on all objects, based on the following attributes: <span class="assign">user data attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_SDI.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_SDI.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_SDI.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall monitor user data stored within the TSC for <span class="assign">integrity errors</span> on all objects, based on the following attributes: <span class="assign">user data attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_SDI.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon detection of a data integrity error, the TSF shall <span class="assign">action to be taken</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UCT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_UCT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to be able to <span class="select">transmit, receive</span> objects in a manner protected from unauthorised disclosure.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_TRP.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_UIT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to be able to <span class="select">transmit, receive</span> user data in a manner protected from <span class="select">modification, deletion, insertion, replay</span> errors.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_UIT.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to determine on receipt of user data, whether <span class="select">modification, deletion, insertion, replay</span> has occurred. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_TRP.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_UIT.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to be able to recover from <span class="assign">list of recoverable errors</span> with the help of the source trusted IT product.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_UIT.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.3">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FDP_UIT.2"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FDP_UIT.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP(s) and/or information flow control SFP(s)</span> to be able to recover from <span class="assign">list of recoverable errors</span> without any help from the source trusted IT product.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_UIT.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_AFL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_AFL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall detect when <span class="assign">number</span> unsuccessful authentication attempts occur related to <span class="assign">list of authentication events</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_AFL.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      When the defined number of unsuccessful authentication attempts has been met or surpassed, the TSF shall <span class="assign">list of actions</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_ATD.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_ATD.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain the following list of security attributes belonging to individual users: <span class="assign">list of security attributes</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_SOS.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_SOS.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a mechanism to verify that secrets meet <span class="assign">a defined quality metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_SOS.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_SOS.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a mechanism to generate secrets that meet <span class="assign">a defined quality metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_SOS.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to enforce the use of TSF generated secrets for <span class="assign">list of TSF functions</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall allow <span class="assign">list of TSF mediated actions</span> on behalf of the user to be performed before the user is authenticated.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require each user to be successfully authenticated before allowing any other TSF-mediated actions on behalf of that user.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require each user to be successfully authenticated before allowing any other TSF-mediated actions on behalf of that user.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">detect, prevent</span> use of authentication data that has been forged by any user of the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">detect, prevent</span> use of authentication data that has been copied from any other user of the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.4">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall prevent reuse of authentication data related to <span class="assign">identified authentication mechanism(s)</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.5">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.5.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">list of multiple authentication mechanisms</span> to support user authentication.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.5.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall authenticate any user's claimed identity according to the <span class="assign">rules describing how the multiple authentication mechanisms provide authentication</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.6">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.6.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall re-authenticate the user under the conditions <span class="assign">list of conditions under which re-authentication is required</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.7">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UAU.7.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide only <span class="assign">list of feedback</span> to the user while the authentication is in progress.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UID.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UID.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall allow <span class="assign">list of TSF-mediated actions</span> on behalf of the user to be performed before the user is identified.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UID.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require each user to be succesfully identified before allowing any other TSF-mediated actions on behalf of that user.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UID.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_UID.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require each user to identify itself before allowing any other TSF-mediated actions on behalf of that user. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_USB.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FIA_USB.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall associate the appropriate user security attributes with subjects acting on behalf of that user.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_ATD.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MOF.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MOF.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the ability to <span class="select">determine the behaviour of, disable, enable, modify the behaviour of</span> the functions <span class="assign">list of functions</span> to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MSA.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP, information flow control SFP</span> to restrict the ability to <span class="select">change_default, query, modify, delete, <span class="assign">other operations</span></span> the security attributes <span class="assign">list of security attributes</span> to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MSA.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that only secure values are accepted for security attributes.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MSA.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the <span class="assign">access control SFP, information flow control SFP</span> to provide <span class="select">restrictive, permissive, other property</span> default values for security attributes that are used to enforce the SFP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MSA.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall allow the <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span> to specify alternative initial values to override the default values when an object or information is created.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MSA.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MTD.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the ability to <span class="select">change_default, query, modify, delete, clear, <span class="assign">other operations</span></span> the <span class="assign">list of TSF data</span> to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MTD.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the specification of the limits for <span class="assign">list of TSF data</span> to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MTD.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall take the following actions, if the TSF data are at, or exceed, the indicated limits: <span class="assign">actions to be taken</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MTD.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_MTD.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that only secure values are accepted for TSF data.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MTD.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_REV.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_REV.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the ability to revoke security attributes associated with the <span class="select">users, subjects, objects, other additional resources</span> within the TSC to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_REV.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce the rules <span class="assign">specification of revocation rules</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SAE.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SAE.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the capability to specify an expiration time for <span class="assign">list of security attributes for which expiration is to be supported</span> to <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SAE.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      For each of these security attributes, the TSF shall be able to <span class="assign">list of actions to be taken for each security attribute</span> after the expiration time for the indicated security attribute has passed.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_STM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain the roles <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to associate users with roles.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain the roles: <span class="assign">the authorised identified roles</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to associate users with roles.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that the conditions <span class="assign">conditions for the different roles</span> are satisfied.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FMT_SMR.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require an explicit request to assume the following roles: <span class="assign">the roles</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_ANO.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_ANO.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine the real user name bound to <span class="assign">list of subjects and/or operations and/or objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_ANO.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPR_ANO.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_ANO.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine the real user name bound to <span class="assign">list of subjects and/or operations and/or objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_ANO.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">list of services</span> to <span class="assign">list of subjects</span> without soliciting any reference to the real user name.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine the real user name bound to <span class="assign">list of subjects and/or operations and/or objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to provide <span class="assign">number of aliases</span> aliases of the real user name to <span class="assign">list of subjects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">determine an alias for a user, accept the alias from the user</span> and verify that it conforms to the <span class="assign">alias metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPR_PSE.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine the real user name bound to <span class="assign">list of subjects and/or operations and/or objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to provide <span class="assign">number of aliases</span> aliases of the real user name to <span class="assign">list of subjects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">determine an alias for a user, accept the alias from the user</span> and verify that it conforms to the <span class="assign">alias metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.2.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="select">an authorised user, <span class="assign">list of trusted subjects</span></span> a capability to determine the user identity based on the provided alias only under the following <span class="assign">list of conditions</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.3">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPR_PSE.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine the real user name bound to <span class="assign">list of subjects and/or operations and/or objects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to provide <span class="assign">number of aliases</span> aliases of the real user name to <span class="assign">list of subjects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.3.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall <span class="select">determine an alias for a user, accept the alias from the user</span> and verify that it conforms to the <span class="assign">alias metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_PSE.3.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide an alias to the real user name which shall be identical to an alias provided previously under the following <span class="assign">list of conditions</span> otherwise the alias provided shall be unrelated to previously provided aliases. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">set of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to determine whether <span class="assign">list of operations</span> <span class="select">were caused by the same user, are related as follows <span class="assign">list of relations</span></span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNO.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">list of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to observe the operation <span class="assign">list of operations</span> on <span class="assign">list of objects</span> by <span class="assign">list of protected users and/or subjects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPR_UNO.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNO.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">list of users and/or subjects</span> are unable to observe the operation <span class="assign">list of operations</span> on <span class="assign">list of objects</span> by <span class="assign">list of protected users and/or subjects</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNO.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall allocate the <span class="assign">unobservability related information</span> among different parts of the TOE such that the following conditions hold during the lifetime of the information: <span class="assign">list of conditions</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNO.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">list of services</span> to <span class="assign">list of subjects</span> without soliciting any reference to <span class="assign">privacy related information</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPR_UNO.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.4">
    <pp.sfr name="FPR_UNO.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide <span class="assign">set of authorised users</span> with the capability to observe the usage of <span class="assign">list of resources and/or services</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_AMT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_AMT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall run a suite of tests <span class="select">during initial start-up, periodically during normal operation, at the request of an authorised user, other conditions</span> to demonstrate the correct operation of the security assumptions provided by the abstract machine that underlies the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_FLS.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_FLS.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall preserve a secure state when the following types of failures occur: <span class="assign">list of types of failures in the TSF</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITA.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITA.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure the availability of <span class="assign">list of types of TSF data</span> provided to a remote trusted IT product within <span class="assign">a defined availability metric</span> given the following conditions <span class="assign">conditions to ensure availability</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall protect all TSF data transmitted from the TSF to a remote trusted IT product from unauthorised disclosure during transmission.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITI.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITI.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to detect modification of all TSF data during transmission between the TSF and a remote trusted IT product within the following metric: <span class="assign">a defined modification metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITI.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to verify the integrity of all TSF data transmitted between the TSF and a remote trusted IT product and perform <span class="assign">action to be taken</span> if modifications are detected.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITI.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_ITI.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITI.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to detect modification of all TSF data during transmission between the TSF and a remote trusted IT product within the following metric: <span class="assign">a defined modification metric</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITI.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to verify the integrity of all TSF data transmitted between the TSF and a remote trusted IT product and perform <span class="assign">action to be taken</span> if modifications are detected.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITI.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to correct <span class="assign">type of modification</span> of all TSF data transmitted between the TSF and a remote trusted IT product.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall protect TSF data from <span class="select">disclosure, modification</span> when it is transmitted between separate parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITT.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall protect TSF data from <span class="select">disclosure, modification</span> when it is transmitted between separate parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITT.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall separate user data from TSF data when such data is transmitted between separate parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITT.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to detect <span class="select">modification of data, substitution of data, re-ordering of data, deletion of data, <span class="assign">other integrity errors</span></span> for TSF data transmitted between separate parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_ITT.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon detection of a data integrity error, the TSF shall take the following actions: <span class="assign">specify the action to be taken</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide unambiguous detection of physical tampering that might compromise the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to determine whether physical tampering with the TSF's devices or TSF's elements has occurred.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MOF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_PHP.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide unambiguous detection of physical tampering that might compromise the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to determine whether physical tampering with the TSF's devices or TSF's elements has occurred.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      For <span class="assign">list of TSF devices/elements for which active detection is required</span>, the TSF shall monitor the devices and elements and notify <span class="assign">a designated user or role</span> when physical tampering with the TSF's devices or TSF's elements has occurred.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FMT_MOF.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_PHP.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall resist <span class="assign">physical tampering scenarios</span> to the <span class="assign">list of TSF devices/elements</span> by responding automatically such that the TSP is not violated.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      After a failure or service discontinuity, the TSF shall enter a maintenance mode where the ability to return the TOE to a secure state is provided.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_TST.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AGD_ADM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_RCV.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      When automated recovery from a failure or service discontinuity is not possible, the TSF shall enter a maintenance mode where the ability to return the TOE to a secure state is provided.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      For <span class="assign">list of failures/service discontinuities</span>, the TSF shall ensure the return of the TOE to a secure state using automated procedures.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_TST.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AGD_ADM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.3">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_RCV.2"/>
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_RCV.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      When automated recovery from a failure or service discontinuity is not possible, the TSF shall enter a maintenance mode where the ability to return the TOE to a secure state is provided.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      For <span class="assign">list of failures/service discontinuities</span>, the TSF shall ensure the return of the TOE to a secure state using automated procedures.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.3.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The functions provided by the TSF to recover from failure or service discontinuity shall ensure that the secure initial state is restored without exceeding <span class="assign">quantification</span> for loss of TSF data or objects within the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.3.4">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to determine the objects that were or were not capable of being recovered. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_TST.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="AGD_ADM.1"/>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.4">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RCV.4.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that <span class="assign">list of SFs and failure scenarios</span> have the property that the SF either completes successfully, or for the indicated failure scenarios, recovers to a consistent and secure state.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="ADV_SPM.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RPL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RPL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall detect replay for the following entities: <span class="assign">list of identified entities</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RPL.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall perform <span class="assign">list of specific actions</span> when replay is detected.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RVM.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_RVM.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that TSP enforcement functions are invoked and succeed before each function within the TSC is allowed to proceed.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain a security domain for its own execution that protects it from interference and tampering by untrusted subjects.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce separation between the security domains of subjects in the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_SEP.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The unisolated portion of the TSF shall maintain a security domain for its own execution that protects it from interference and tampering by untrusted subjects.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce separation between the security domains of subjects in the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.2.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain the part of the TSF related to <span class="assign">list of access control and/or information flow control SFPs</span> in a security domain for their own execution that protects them from interference and tampering by the remainder of the TSF and by subjects untrusted with respect to those SFPs.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.3">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_SEP.2"/>
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_SEP.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The unisolated portion of the TSF shall maintain a security domain for its own execution that protects it from interference and tampering by untrusted subjects.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.3.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce separation between the security domains of subjects in the TSC.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SEP.3.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall maintain the part of the TSF that enforces the access control and/or information flow control SFPs in a security domain for its own execution that protects them from interference and tampering by the remainder of the TSF and by subjects untrusted with respect to the TSP.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SSP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SSP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall acknowledge, when requested by another part of the TSF, the receipt of an unmodified TSF data transmission. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SSP.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FPT_SSP.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SSP.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall acknowledge, when requested by another part of the TSF, the receipt of an unmodified TSF data transmission. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_SSP.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that the relevant parts of the TSF know the correct status of transmitted data among its different parts, using acknowledgements.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_STM.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_STM.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to provide reliable time stamps for its own use. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TDC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TDC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide the capability to consistently interpret <span class="assign">list of TSF data types</span> when shared between the TSF and another trusted IT product.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TDC.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall use <span class="assign">list of interpretation rules to be applied by the TSF</span> when interpreting the TSF data from another trusted IT product. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TRC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TRC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that TSF data is consistent when replicated between parts of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TRC.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      When parts of the TOE containing replicated TSF data are disconnected, the TSF shall ensure the consistency of the replicated TSF data upon reconnection before processing any requests for <span class="assign">list of SFs dependent on TSF data replication consistency</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TST.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TST.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall run a suite of self tests <span class="select">during initial start-up, periodically during normal operation, at the request of the authorised user, at the conditions <span class="assign">conditions under which self test should occur</span></span> to demonstrate the correct operation of the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TST.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide authorised users with the capability to verify the integrity of TSF data. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FPT_TST.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide authorised users with the capability to verify the integrity of stored TSF executable code.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_AMT.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_FLT.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_FLT.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure the operation of <span class="assign">list of TOE capabilities</span> when the following failures occur: <span class="assign">list of type of failures</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_FLS.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_FLT.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FRU_FLT.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_FLT.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure the operation of all the TOE's capabilities when the following failures occur :<span class="assign">list of type of failures</span>. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FPT_FLS.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_PRS.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_PRS.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall assign a priority to each subject in the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_PRS.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that each access to <span class="assign">controlled resources</span> shall be mediated on the basis of the subjects assigned priority.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_PRS.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FRU_PRS.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_PRS.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall assign a priority to each subject in the TSF.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_PRS.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure that each access to all shareable resources shall be mediated on the basis of the subjects assigned priority.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_RSA.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_RSA.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce maximum quotas of the following resources: <span class="assign">controlled resources</span> that <span class="select">individual user, defined group of users, subjects</span> can use <span class="select">simultaneously, over a specified period of time</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_RSA.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FRU_RSA.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_RSA.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce maximum quotas of the following resources <span class="assign">controlled resources</span> that <span class="select">individual user, defined group of users</span> can use <span class="select">simultaneously, over a specified period of time</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FRU_RSA.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall ensure the provision of minimum quantity of each <span class="assign">controlled resource</span> that is available for <span class="select">an individual user, defined group of users, subjects</span> to use <span class="select">simultaneously, over a specified period of time</span>
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_LSA.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_LSA.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the scope of the session security attributes <span class="assign">session security attributes</span>, based on <span class="assign">attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_MCS.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_MCS.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the maximum number of concurrent sessions that belong to the same user.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_MCS.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce, by default, a limit of <span class="assign">default number</span> sessions per user. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_MCS.2">
    <pp.sfrs.superscedes name="FTA_MCS.1"/>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_MCS.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall restrict the maximum number of concurrent sessions that belong to the same user according to the rules <span class="assign">rules for the number of maximum concurrent sessions</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_MCS.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall enforce, by default, a limit of <span class="assign">default number</span> sessions per user. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UID.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_SSL.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall lock an interactive session after <span class="assign">time interval of user inactivity</span> by:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	clearing or overwriting display devices, making the current contents unreadable;
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	disabling any activity of the user's data access/display devices other than unlocking the session.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_SSL.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require the following events to occur prior to unlocking the session: <span class="assign">events to occur</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.2">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_SSL.2.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall allow user-initiated locking of the user's own interactive session, by:
      </p>
        <ol>
          <li>
      <p>
	clearing or overwriting display devices, making the current contents unreadable;
	</p>
      </li>
          <li>
      <p>
	disabling any activity of the user's data access/display devices other than unlocking the session.
	</p>
      </li>
        </ol>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_SSL.2.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require the following events to occur prior to unlocking the session: <span class="assign">events to occur</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
      <pp.sfr.dependency name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.3">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_SSL.3.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall terminate an interactive session after a <span class="assign">time interval of user inactivity</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TAB.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_TAB.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Before establishing a user session, the TSF shall display an advisory warning message regarding unauthorised use of the TOE.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TAH.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_TAH.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon successful session establishment, the TSF shall display the <span class="select">date, time, method, location</span> of the last successful session establishment to the user. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_TAH.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      Upon successful session establishment, the TSF shall display the <span class="select">date, time, method, location</span> of the last unsuccessful attempt to session establishment and the number of unsuccessful attempts since the last successful session establishment. 
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_TAH.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall not erase the access history information from the user interface without giving the user an opportunity to review the information.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TSE.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTA_TSE.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall be able to deny session establishment based on <span class="assign">attributes</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTP_ITC.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_ITC.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a communication channel between itself and a remote trusted IT product that is logically distinct from other communication channels and provides assured identification of its end points and protection of the channel data from modification or disclosure.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_ITC.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit <span class="select">the TSF, the remote trusted IT product</span> to initiate communication via the trusted channel.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_ITC.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall initiate communication via the trusted channel for <span class="assign">list of functions for which a trusted channel is required</span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTP_TRP.1">
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_TRP.1.1">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall provide a communication path between itself and <span class="select">remote, local</span> users that is logically distinct from other communication paths and provides assured identification of its end points and protection of the communicated data from modification or disclosure.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_TRP.1.2">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall permit <span class="select">the TSF, local users, remote users</span> to initiate communication via the trusted path.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
    <pp.sfr name="FTP_TRP.1.3">
      <pp.description>
        <p>
      The TSF shall require the use of the trusted path for <span class="select">initial user authentication, <span class="assign">other services for which trusted path is required</span></span>.
      </p>
      </pp.description>
    </pp.sfr>
  </pp.sfrs>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_ARP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_GEN.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_GEN.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAA.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SAR.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_SEL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FAU_STG.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRO.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRO.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRR.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCO_NRR.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_CKM.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FCS_COP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACC.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ACF.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_DAU.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_DAU.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ETC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ETC.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFC.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.5"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_IFF.6"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITC.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ITT.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_RIP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_RIP.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ROL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_ROL.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_SDI.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_SDI.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UCT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FDP_UIT.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_AFL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_ATD.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_SOS.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_SOS.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.5"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.6"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UAU.7"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UID.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_UID.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FIA_USB.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MOF.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MSA.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_MTD.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_REV.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SAE.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FMT_SMR.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_ANO.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_ANO.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_PSE.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPR_UNO.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_AMT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_FLS.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITA.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITI.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITI.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_ITT.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_PHP.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RCV.4"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RPL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_RVM.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SEP.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SSP.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_SSP.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_STM.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TDC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TRC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FPT_TST.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_FLT.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_FLT.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_PRS.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_PRS.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_RSA.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FRU_RSA.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_LSA.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_MCS.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_MCS.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.2"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_SSL.3"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TAB.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TAH.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTA_TSE.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTP_ITC.1"/>
  <pp.sfrs name="FTP_TRP.1"/>
</pp.it.functional>
